Let go of me...
Stop it...
She's the only daughter we have left.
Did you kill Emma?
How dare you try to steal my daughter!
I'm going to kill you!
Elsa!
Help!
Stay back!
Find an excuse and leave.
But...
Elsa...
The number you called cannot be connected.
Please call back later.
(Ngan Kai Bay Pier)
Why did Dr. Hong take three weeks off?
Dr. Hong didn't really say.
Please come this way.
Thanks.
Kwan Sir, looks very empty.
What do you know about his family?
He has a pretty wife and two daughters.
He has a family portrait.
He took it with him?
It's OK. Do you know their names?
I only know his wife is Mia.
The older daughter is Emma,
the younger one is Elsa.
Emma?
Emma Hong, Hong Ka-lam.
That's EH on the watchband.
C628, with the initials EH engraved
on the watchband.
Chan Lap-jim, James, right?
You're the faceless corpse Emma's boyfriend?
Yes.
A customer of the store said
he saw a tall man wearing
a dark green windbreaker
chasing someone like Emma near
where her body was found.
You have a similar build.
We also found on social media
you have a dark green windbreaker.
I'm not the only one who has it.
Emma's father has one too.
I'll get one for Daddy.
Good.
Why did Emma have to smuggle
out of Hong Kong?
She wanted to be in the UK with me.
But...she doesn't have an ID card.
As expected, she was undocumented.
What else did Emma say about her father?
Emma was very protective of her family.
I really don't know.
I remember...about six months ago,
Emma told me she had a chocolate cyst.
She said it hurt like hell.
I was worried about her
and told her to go see a doctor.
She told me not to worry
because her father will fix it.
Later, she told me it didn't hurt anymore.
Chocolate cyst.
When we went to the hospital
to ask Hong Lik about the faceless corpse
and chocolate cyst,
he seemed very calm and composed.
But I noticed one thing,
when we showed him the picture
of the body,
he had a strong reaction.
As a doctor, he should be used to
something gory.
He shouldn't have looked so surprised.
The only reason for his reaction
was he knew we're talking about
his daughter.
No wonder the victim had no ID
but had access to prescription drugs
for her chocolate cyst.
Hong Lik and his family had so much to hide.
Based on Chan Lap-jim's statement,
I have reasons to believe Hong Lik
is a violent person
and an authoritative father.
To prevent exposing the family
for having no IDs,
he killed his rebellious older daughter.
Let's go to Ching Sir.
Where's my phone?
You're awake?
You haven't eaten in over ten hours.
You must be hungry. Eat this.
Why did you give me a shot?
Why did you tie me up?
You found out I had Emma's phone.
You must have a lot of questions
and won't come with us quietly.
But we must leave tonight.
I had no choice but to do this.
Did you kill Emma?
Whatever you want to know,
after we settle down,
I will tell you everything, OK?
If you won't tell me, you must have done it.
Why? How did you kill Emma?
She was your flesh and blood.
How could you do it?
Will you calm down? You just woke up,
I don't want to give you another shot.
Just listen to me and behave.
We're not far from where we should
board the boat.
Eat your food and get some rest
and get your strength back.
We'll be on the boat for a long time.
You creep! You killed Emma!
I'm not going with you.
It's very high!
Climb down!
It's so high!
We're dead if you don't.
Here goes nothing.
Elsa...
Elsa!
Wait here for me!
Elsa, come back!
Elsa...
Help...
Elsa...stop running! Elsa!
Stay back!
Don't step back...it's dangerous!
Let me go...
Let me go, you creep!
Listen to me...
I'm not leaving with you.
Stop it, calm down...
I won't go with you.
Don't move!
Let go of me...
Stop it or I'll give you a shot.
Get me the needle...
Let go. She's the only daughter we have...
Mom!
You want to see this happen again?
Daddy killed Emma, right?
Mom, you knew about this?
You knew he killed Emma?
Elsa...
I'm asking you! Yes or no?
Are you crazy?
Emma was your daughter.
She only ran away from home,
why did you kill her?
And you lied to me!
Why do I have parents like you?
You killed your own daughter!
Tell me. Why did you kill Emma?
How did she die?
Emma's death had nothing to do with Mom.
Don't blame her.
The day Emma left,
I was anxious to find her.
I paid a hacker
to turn on her old phone
and found out she had a boyfriend
in the UK called James.
I figure since Emma didn't have an ID,
she couldn't possibly leave town legally.
Since she took so much money from me,
she's likely to smuggle to the UK
to be with her boyfriend.
I called up a patient from a few years ago
who's in the triad
to find out if Emma was leaving
on a speedboat.
Three days after Emma left,
my triad friend finally found something.
Hello, Dr. Hong, I found out for you.
Tonight, a girl called Emma
will get on the boat from a pier
code named Meow Lung Kee.
Before they board the speedboat,
Meow Lung Kee will arrange for their
passengers to wait in Bo On Hotel
in Tsimshatsui.
So I looked for her at Bo On Hotel.
Is the girl in Room 3 around?
She went out.
Emma!
Emma...
Don't run!
Let go of me!
Come home with me...
That house is like a prison.
Nobody had any say in that house.
I don't want to be your slave.
Emma!
Help, he's trying to kidnap me!
Emma, come back!
Why are you chasing that girl?
You better watch it!
What do you want?
We're calling the Police...
I didn't want to make a scene in public.
So I decided to bring her home
before she boarded the boat at Meow Lung Kee
I know Meow Lung Kee is Ngan Kai Bay pier.
The boat wasn't there yet when
I arrived at the pier.
So I looked for Emma nearby
hoping to intercept her.
You're breaking up, reception is poor.
OK, bye!
Emma...come back!
Emma!
Stay back!
Don't move! Stop! It's dangerous!
I'd rather fall to death than
go home with you.
OK, I won't chase you...Come back in...
That's a lie. I don't believe you.
Emma...
Help me, Daddy!
I can't hold on...
Emma, grab my hand, don't let go. Emma...
I can't...
Emma...
Emma!
Emma...are you OK?
It hurts...
Don't worry, let me examine you.
If I listened to you,
I wouldn't end up like this.
I'm sorry, Daddy!
My leg hurts.
Here?
It's a fracture. Should be nothing major.
Don't worry, I have a first aid kit
in the car.
I'll go get it.
Bear with me and wait here.
OK, I dressed your wound
and gave you a shot for the pain.
The pain is going away, right?
Daddy, I want to go home.
OK, I'll take you home.
Emma...
Emma...what happened?
Emma!
Emma is gone.
Emma, please don't die.
Emma, don't leave me, OK?
Emma...
Felix, how did Emma die?
Oh God!
We need to call the Police.
No Police!
What if they arrest you and Elsa?
I'll go buy some tools
and find a place to bury Emma.
Mom and I left Emma on the slope
and went to buy some tools.
But when we came back,
Emma's face was all torn up.
We also saw footprints of a wild boar.
I bet the wild boar chewed up her face.
I buried her by myself.
I gathered the money and took her phone...
and burnt everything else.
We didn't want to break your heart
and decided not to tell you.
I was afraid you'd call the Police.
I also wanted to buy some time
so I can take you and your Mom
away from Hong Kong.
I just didn't expect Emma's body
would be discovered so quickly.
What is it?
But you knew right away...
It's Emma.
...the faceless corpse was Emma.
I was afraid the Police will be
at our front door soon.
But then again, Emma's face
was all torn up
and her identity has not been documented.
The Police may not link her to us.
But I noticed you were texting Emma
on Chat App,
I guess you already suspect
Emma was dead.
To make you give up,
while you were cooking in the kitchen,
I asked Mom to use Emma's new phone
to text you saying she was safe.
It's Emma!
Then I stepped into the kitchen
and pretended I caught you
getting a message from Emma,
and told you to go tell your Mom.
She was emotionally unstable at the time.
I had to console her.
Luckily, you didn't catch on
and Mom and I were so relieved.
After the way things turned out,
I had to take you and Mom away ASAP.
I didn't expect the Police
to show up at the hospital
and ask me about the chocolate cyst.
Though I pretended I didn't recognize
the faceless corpse,
I knew the Police will catch on
sooner or later
I stole the drugs from the hospital
and gave them to Emma.
When the Police showed me Emma's picture,
it reminded me of how Emma died.
I felt as if I was stabbed in the heart.
If only Emma believed me,
none of this would have happened.
If you didn't pressure her and chase her,
she'd be fine.
You still don't think you were responsible?
Not that I don't think I'm responsible,
I just didn't expect
things to turn out like this.
Elsa, Daddy might have been strict
with you and Emma,
he only did it for your own good.
He already did all he could.
Emma is dead,
have you any idea how heartbroken he was?
He couldn't sleep at night.
So? Heartbroken or not,
if he hadn't been so fierce with Emma,
she wouldn't be dead
and I wouldn't have lost my sister.
I hate you. I'll never forgive you.
Elsa, please!
I already lost Emma,
I can't lose you and your Daddy.
I don't want to live anymore.
Please don't leave me.
Please come with us.
I'm untying you.
We're boarding the boat at 8 o'clock.
It's a 30-minute walk from here
to the pier.
Then we'll be on the boat for a long time.
Get some rest.
I want my phone back.
I'll give it back when we land over there.
I just remember a hacker friend
recommended a tracker app.
Click this link...
click it and I can hack into your phone.
I'll know your location wherever you are.
Really? That's great!
Look!
You're right! That's great!
I have never seen anyone so happy
about being hacked.
(Ngan Kai Bay Pier)
Is Elsa locked up in here?
Police!
Kwan sir,
Hong Lik and his family
seem to have skipped town.
Ask Ching Sir to issue a warrant.
Let's check for any leads.
Yes, Sir!
Elsa...
I finally found you!
I thought I'll never see you again.
Did your father kill your sister?
Let's go.
No! I can't.
Your father will kill you too.
Emma's death was an accident.
Daddy didn't mean to kill her.
He's not heartless.
I promised Mom I'll go with her.
What are you doing here?
Elsa agreed to come with us.
How dare you try to steal my daughter!
I'm going to kill you!
Stop it...
No...
YY won't hurt us...
Out of my way...
Elsa!
No!
Out of my way or I'll hit you too.
You already killed Emma.
I won't let you hurt YY.
Felix, stop it!
Elsa, get on the boat!
Mia...
YY, take care of Elsa.
No!
What?
Don't get on the boat!
Why?
If your Mom can't hold off your father,
or it was their act
to con you into boarding the boat,
you'll be in grave danger.
If I can't get on the boat
and I can't go home.
What should I do?
Let's get out of here.
They won't catch up with us.
Let's sit down.
Well? Did Daddy hurt you?
I'm fine.
But your father was...
I have never seen him so ferocious!
The way I ran out on them,
I may never see them again.
You still have me.
We'll be together, OK?
How? I have no ID.
Nobody knew about you before.
We can do it too.
Though I don't know what
our future holds,
I believe as long as we're together,
we won't have a problem.
Maybe we can be together...
for 10...20...30 years or even forever.
It'll be unfair to you,
when you're with me,
you'll need to live your life in the shadow.
As long as we're together,
nothing else matters.
After we finish eating,
we'll take a taxi to my place.
You can sleep in my room.
I'll take the living room.
I'll get new furniture
so you can live more comfortably.
Don't worry, I'll ease into it.
We have late breaking news.
Famous obstetrician and gynecologist
Dr. Hong Lik
has been arrested for the
murder of his daughter.
The Police confirmed his daughter
was the victim in the sensational
faceless corpse case.
Allegedly, the victim's identity and birth
have never been documented...
What happened?
It's from Daddy.
How could he send me a message?
He must have pre-recorded a delayed message.
Elsa, when you get this recording,
you should be on the boat.
Earlier on,
I saw on the surveillance app on my phone,
maybe because of Emma,
the Police already searched our house.
They should soon find the village house.
What should we do now?
The key is to protect you and Elsa.
The cops want to arrest me because of Emma.
If they have me,
they probably won't come after you.
I saw the reporter climb upstairs.
He probably wanted to save Elsa.
Let him take you and Elsa on the boat.
I'm staying.
Let the Police arrest me too.
I'm not afraid of going to jail.
I don't want Elsa involved.
I know our daughter well.
She loves me. She won't leave with the boy.
I have an idea.
Find a chance to give this back to her.
Don't barge in so quickly. Wait a while.
What are you doing here?
Elsa agreed to come with us.
How dare you try to steal my daughter!
I'm going to kill you!
No, Daddy...
After we're arrested,
the Police probably won't search nearby,
you should be safe.
I hope this can buy you some time
for you to board the boat safely.
Even if you can't get on the boat,
when Mom and I turn ourselves in,
we should be able to get you
the status of a Hong Kong resident.
Anyway...you and Emma are the two people
your Mom and I loved the most
in this world.
I'm willing to do anything for you.
Perhaps my way is not to your liking.
That's why we ended up like this.
I really regret it.
For over twenty years,
your Mom and I might have
made a lot of mistakes,
that's why we turned ourselves in
to get the punishment we deserved.
Don't be unhappy.
The boy just now risked his life for you.
Your Mom and I are happy
to have him look after you.
Wherever you maybe,
I hope you'll always be happy.
Even if we never see you again,
we'll have nothing to worry about.
(Wise men say only fools rush in)
(For I can't help falling in love with you)
Dr. Hong, you're suspected of murder.
You're now under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you wish to say
will be jotted down
and may be used as evidence in court.
Miss Hong Ka-yee,
did the victim Hong Ka-lam
often argue with her father Hong Lik?
And was locked up in her room by him
for almost a month?
Has Hong Lik been physically violent
towards her?
Yes...right before my sister left home,
she often had fights with my father.
But for over twenty years,
our family got along very well
with each other.
We almost never had any arguments.
How did you get along?
Our background is rather complicated.
Mom, my sister and I are undocumented.
My sister and I did not have
the freedom other kids have,
we can't go to school
or borrow books from the library
or meet anyone we like.
But while we were growing up,
Daddy and Mom love us very much.
Whatever we wanted,
they'd try hard to satisfy us,
letting us learn different things.
Daddy is a doctor,
no matter how busy he was,
he tried to make time for us,
teaching us how to read and write
and played with us.
My sister's death was a tragedy.
Though our childhood was different
from other kids,
I felt I was fortunate enough
to be born into a family like this
and grew up with my parents' love.
I'm sure my sister would think so too.
Regarding the charge of manslaughter
of Hong Ka-lam by her father Hong Lik
and the charge of preventing the lawful
burial of a body against Pak Mei-nga,
will the Jury please give us your verdict?
Your Honor, we have a unanimous verdict,
we find the first defendant Hong Lik
not guilty of manslaughter.
I can't believe you stayed.
I didn't know what you did was
for my own good.
I thought you and Mom only loved each other.
I never expected, for my sake,
you'd stay behind and turn yourself in.
Now, you are forced to be apart.
I let you down, I'm sorry.
You're my daughter,
I'll do anything for you.
The same goes for your Mom.
Luckily, you're both found guilty only of
preventing the lawful burial of a body
and not documenting our identities.
You'll be out in two years.
Two years will go by quickly.
Actually...I should serve
more than two years.
Daddy, Emma's death was an accident.
Stop blaming yourself.
No, I am responsible for her death.
Why?
I haven't told you the whole story.
Emma...
I can't hold on...
Emma...are you OK?
It hurts...
Don't worry, let me examine you.
It's a fracture. Should be nothing major.
No need to call the Police.
I can handle it.
Emma...
Emma, why didn't I notice
you have internal bleeding?
I should have called an ambulance.
I killed you, Emma...
I misjudged the severity of her condition.
If I had called an ambulance,
Emma wouldn't have died.
I was selfish and didn't want
the Police involved...
Your hands were shaking last time
because you prescribed the wrong
drugs for a patient.
It wasn't the guilt you felt towards
the patient,
but because it reminded you
of misjudging Emma's injuries.
After Emma died,
in order to hide the truth from you,
I refused to believe I killed her.
But deep down, I knew all along.
I killed your sister.
Daddy, Emma was so seriously injured,
even if you called an ambulance,
she still couldn't have made it.
The result would have been the same.
It's time you let it go.
Promise me.
When Mom gets out, we can be reunited.
In the days ahead, you must
take care of yourself, OK?
OK!
YY helped me apply for proof of identity.
I can now openly walk down the streets.
It's OK, just fill this out for me...
Elsa, since you're scared.
You can sleep with me.
Great!
QQ will keep you company too.
Miss, you wish to apply for
this virtual credit card?
If I apply for it, I'll get this suitcase?
Yes, but while stocks last.
I want to apply.
Please come this way.
Your ID card please?
A photocopy?
Yes...does that work?
It's OK...
It's just a recognizance form.
That's still proof of identity.
Stop toying with us.
I should get my ID card soon.
When you get your official ID card,
you can look us up.
But I really want this suitcase.
I also want my own credit card.
I will submit it later.
Come back to us later.
We'll wait for you.
Sir, would you like to apply
for our virtual credit card?
(A few weeks later)
Hi, Emma.
I'm still not used to life without you.
Mom is getting out in six months.
She'll be repatriated to her hometown.
But the Hong Kong government won't
restrict her from coming back.
She'll come back to Hong Kong
using the proper channels.
When Daddy finished serving his
remaining 18 months,
we can be reunited.
I have another piece of good news.
Because I was born in Hong Kong,
and Daddy and Mom took so many
videos and pictures of us,
our piano teacher Miss Louise
and all our neighbors can vouch for me
that I have been living in Hong Kong
for many years,
Immigration used their discretion.
See?
I finally have a Hong Kong ID card.
I'm officially a Hong Kong resident.
Emma, before you left home,
you said out here, you can go
anywhere you like
and you promised to show me the world.
The other day, someone was
promoting a credit card
and they were giving away a suitcase
which had your favorite
cartoon character on it.
I thought if we could both have an ID card,
go on a trip together and start a new life,
wouldn't that be great?
I guess we'll never have the chance.
Because of your sacrifice,
I now enjoy the happiness you want
me to have.
Thanks, Emma.
I'll always love you.
Did you find the band room?
Shall I go with you?
I was on the wrong floor.
It should be the 9/F, don't worry.
I found it. Get back to work.
OK, be careful. Bye!
No...yes...push!
Two more steps...
1...2...
Almost...
Stop! Gotcha!
What is it, Miss?
You work for Bountiful Virtual Bank, right?
You had a pop-up stand promoting
a credit card.
I went back there several times
but couldn't find you.
Now I have my official ID card,
can I still apply for the credit card?
Is the suitcase still available?
The promotion is over. No more.
We'll call you next time.
Next time? When is that?
Will they still have the suitcase?
Miss, you're too heavy.
Please step outside, OK?
Please?
Heavy? Me? Not as heavy as your crate.
It's huge. What's inside?